How to get two wheeler insurance through CSC
?  Hello friends, you are watching
BVM CSC V.  So let's start the video.  First of all, by
clicking on Motor Corporation,
you will get insurance through every bank here.
[sound of clearing throat] So here we are going to go
through ICI Bank.  So here
you will see two wheeler, you have to click on TP on it.
Here, first of all you have to
enter your vehicle number and registration number and click on the gate.  It takes up
all your data.  Here we are going to do
three years insurance.  So
here we will select 3 years and click on Gate.
Here a
payment of ₹3763 is shown which is
allowed for three years.  Click on the process.
Here you start seeing the complete details.
Now here we are going to do eKYC.
Let's click on eKYC.
Here you will see that there is an option of Other.
After this you have to upload the documents in it
like.  So here, as soon as you
upload the documents,
some search will start happening here.  After that, we will
give you complete details here according to their Aadhar.
So let us enter their details.
After entering, you will see that
you have to select the name gender here.
Sir, you have to make the selection.  Here
you will enter their customer's mobile number
and PAN card also has to be entered here.
So let us see the further process after entering the PAN card here.
So if we process here and
look here, some air problem is visible.
So if you look here, you are
also being asked for your email ID.  So let's
enter the email ID here also.  Still,
after entering the email ID, you will still
click on Process Gate here.  Still the air will come.  This is something to pay
special attention to.  So
we will also tell you what you need to pay attention to in this.  So if you
look here, first of all
you will select your name, address and then
click on process, then
your process will be done.  Here,
as soon as you click on Pay Now, your
payment gets ready.  You have to
enter the CSC wallet PIN here.  After entering,
you also have to click on validate.
As soon as you click on Validate, you will be
asked for your CSC Wallet PIN.  Here you
can get the payment deducted.  So as soon as you
enter the wallet PIN and click on Pay Now,
your payment becomes successful here.
After this, a receipt is issued to the customer.
From here you can download the PDF and
print it and give it to the customer very easily.  If
you liked this small information then please
like the video.  If you are on the channel for the first time then please
subscribe to the channel also.
Let's meet in the next video
with a new topic.  So that was my video for today
and don't forget to share it with your friends
and comment in the comment section.